You are currently in the Editor mode of the FDOrganizer.
Here you can manage your data.
For example, you can structure it or add metadata.
To prepare your data for the long-term availability,
you first need to create a new project.
To do this, use the Add project button.
There are two ways to create a new project.
Either you can create an empty project
or you can import your data directly from a zip file.
For an empty project, make sure you select the correct option and then assign a name.
When you press the Create project button, it will be created.
If you want to choose the second option and import your data directly from a zip file,
use also the Add project button
and select the option „Import from zip“.
Use the plus sign to select your zip file.
Your file explorer will then open in a new window.
Here you can select the zip file you want to use
and upload it to the FDOrganizer by using the Open button.
When you click the Import zip button,
your new project is created containing the data from your zip file.
You can change the name of your project by using the pencil icon next to the current name.
If you want to cancel your name change and keep your original name, click on the cross.
To confirm your name change, use the check mark
and the new name will be applied to the current project.
If necessary, you can remove the whole project by using the recycle bin symbol.
When you click on the symbol, a dialogue box will offer you two options.
You can either leave your project unchanged.
Or you can permanently delete it.
Please note that in this case, all of the data contained in that project
will also be deleted and cannot be recovered.